Hello Mr Snail, oh you cute little corny was sparesome, that name, bonus points.
Can't believe we got stuck with a tree hugger, if I have to hear the Latin name for one more animal I swear I'm gonna kill her.
Relax sugar buns, while she does all the work we'll have all the fun.
Yeah and get wasted out of our minds, where are you man?
Come on team, we mustn't dilly-dally when there's so much nature to see.
I was thinking we should call our class project Fun Guys in a Forest.
Get it? Because we're a group of fun guys and also fun guys.
Shush, that's the yellow bird team and she's in distress.
There there are little monsters in a flower.
Oh, look at her go.
Wow.
Out of the way talk one, we're camping here.
Finally, time to get that barbecue burning.
Oh dear.
Easy guys, we're supposed to be studying nature not wrecking it.
Kiss break.
Oi, fungus freak, make yourself usable and fix the tent.
Oh, a bit of friendly campsite ribbing.
Fun asked.
She wouldn't survive five minutes alone in these woods.
Yeah, she's a real weenie that one, isn't it?
Oi, Phil, no sausages coming.
Almost ready.
We need a bit more salt.
Huh?
It's incredible, it's a new species.
What the bloody hell are those things?
It's like a no shag to mushrooms.
They're absolutely adorable.
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable and I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things.
We'd be famous.
Get on MTV, I wonder what they taste like.
Oh, we really shouldn't disrupt their habitat.
Right, sure, sure.
Greetings.
Welcome friends, I'll be right down.
Could I interest you in some peppermint tea?
What are you guys?
We are sprites, we sprite balance to the forest.
We take care of the animals.
What?
Guys, guys.
Hey, little mushroom geezer, you call with us camping here for the night?
Absolutely, a friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites.
Maybe, maybe it was just ketchup or something like red paint?
Yeah, maybe they were just painting their little hats or something.
Guys?
Guys, this isn't funny.
We're just going to catch one with their psycho.
They've got to get me out of these hurry, they're going to kill us.
Ready, ready, go.
Hurry.
We'll leap and stroll.
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches.
Sprite time.
Sprite.
She has a wife to help me!
Help me!
Oh!
Oh, no!
Sweet cake!
Oh!
Ah!
What?
Is that?
No!
No, no, no!
Oh!
I can't swim!
No!
No one has gone away.
What?
No!
No, no, no!
So,
Yes, Yes!
No! No!
S
All right then, eat salty little green bastards!
Those punks treated the world as their own personal rubbish bin, and you set them free!
Now you'll join them!
I'll give you that one, brother bird!
All right, sprites, let's burn the bunnies and have some peppermint tea!
Give things up, where are we wrong? Die, be die, Billy, before it steals our happy home! We all together now!
It's friendly, sprite, sprite, is it the sun? It's friendly, be sprite, be the moon?
It's friendly, aye, aye, aye, yum, yum!
Danger, danger, I'm a forest ranger, about and clear the way!
I'm about to blast this dick like plastic, what ya mama gonna say?
I'm about to drop it, stanky, drop it, I'ma just catch in steam!
Now pillage, and loot it, I'ma pollute it, lake to the river to the stream for spawn!
Follow a little deary, then call me cavalry, try to cut me down to size!
Now there's my announcer, driver, bouncer, bacon, meat, cakes, and pies! This camp is a call out, here come the fallout, me and my crew don't play!
My boots on the log, on the leaf, on the frog, cut walls in the tree to say, hey, hey, hey!
City kid, city kid rock, city kid rock!
You