Hello, Mr. Snail. Oh, you cute, little, corn-ewisper-some. Latin name. Bonus points.
Can't believe we got stuck with a tree hugger. If I have to hear the Latin name for one more animal, I swear I'm gonna kill her.
Relax, sugar buns. While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun.
Yeah, and get wasted out of our minds. Way ahead of you, man.
Come on, team. We mustn't dilly-dally when there's so much nature to see.
I was thinking we should call our class project Fungi's in a Forest. Get it? Because we're a group of fun guys and also fun guys.
Shush! That's a low word, team. And she's in distress. There, there, my little Monticello flower.
Oh, look at her go. Wow.
Out of the way, dorkwad. We're camping here.
Finally. Time to get that barbecue burning.
Oh, oh dear.
Gross.
Easy, guys. We're supposed to be studying nature, not wrecking it.
Piss break.
Oh, dear.
Oi, fungus freak. Make yourself usable and fix the tent.
Oh, a bit of friendly campsite ribbing. Fun.
She wouldn't survive five minutes alone in these woods.
Yeah, she's a real weenie, that one, innit?
Oi, Phil. I know sausage is coming.
Almost ready. Just need a bit more salt.
It's incredible. It's a new species.
What the bloody hell are those things? It's like a no shagged a mushroom.
Friendly bees, friendly gums. We won't stop till the day is fun.
Friendly yi yi yi yum yum. We can watch wherever we run.
Friendly bees, friendly gums.
They're absolutely adorable. Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable.
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things.
We'll be famous. Get on MTV. I wonder what they taste like.
Oh, we really shouldn't disrupt their habitat.
Sure, sure.
Greetings. Welcome, friends. I'll be right down.
Could I interest you in some peppermint tea?
What are you guys?
We are Sprites. We sprite balance to the forest.
We take care of the animals. Squants, birds, moths, baby bugs.
Guys, guys.
Hey, little mushroom geezer. You cool with us camping here for the night?
Absolutely. A friend of the forest is a friend of the Sprites.
Maybe, maybe it was just ketchup or something like red paint.
Yeah, maybe they were just painting their little hats or something.
Guys?
Guys, this isn't funny.
We were just going to catch one, but they're psycho.
They've got to get me out of these hurry. They're going to kill us.
Sprite, we go.
Hurry.
They've been left for leaf and stone.
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches.
Sprite time.
You little freaks.
Sprite this.
Help, my heart.
Are you okay?
Sprite, help me.
Sugarbunch, Sugarbunch, help me.
Help me.
Sweet cake.
No, stop it.
What?
Is that?
No, no, no.
I can't swim.
Yes, yes.
No, no.
Sugarbunch, Sprite's here.
Surprise.
I don't want to hurt you. Just keep your distance.
All right then.
Eat salty little green bastards.
Those punks treated the world as their own personal rubbish bin and you set them free.
Now you'll join them.
I'll give you that one, Brother Bird.
All right, Sprites, let's burn the bodies and have some peppermint tea.
I'm giving lunch where ever we roam. Die-dee, die-dee, Billy, the forest is our happy home. Pull, pull, ha-ha, we all together now.
Stride, loose, Sprite, Sprite, slick the sun. Strang-dee-dee, Strang-dee-dum. We won't stop till the day is fun.
Strang-dee, yi-yi-yi, yum-yum.
Danger, danger, I'm a forest ranger. Up out and clear the way.
I'm about to blast this dick like plastic. What your mama gonna say?
I'm about to drop it, stanky, plop it. I'ma just catch in steam.
Now pillage and loot it. I'ma pollute it. Lake to the river, to the stream, posposh.
Pull a little deerie and call me Cavalierie. Try to cut me down to size.
Well, there's my announcer, driver, bouncer, baking me cakes and pies.
Yeah, this camp is a call-out. Here come the fallout. Me and my crew don't play.
My blues on the log, on the leaf, on the frog. Cut words in the tree to say, hey, hey, hey.
City get rough, city get rough. City get rough, city get rough.