I can't believe we got stuck with the tree.
If I have to hear the Latin name for one more animal, I swear I'm gonna kill her.
Relax, sugar buns. While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun.
Yeah, and get wasted out of our minds. Way ahead of you, man.
Come on, team. We mustn't dilly-dally when there's so much nature to see.
I was thinking, we should call our class project Fungi's in a forest.
Get it? Because we're a group of fun guys and also fun guys.
Shush! There'll be no work, team. And she's in distress.
There then, little Monticello Flava.
Oh, look at her go. Wow.
Out of the way, dorkwad. We're camping here.
Finally. Time to get that barbecue burning.
Oh, oh dear.
Easy, guys. We're supposed to be studying nature, not wrecking it.
Piss break.
Oi, fungus free. Make yourself useful and fix the tent.
Oh, a bit of friendly campsite ribbing. Fun.
She wouldn't survive five minutes alone in these woods.
Yeah, she's a real weenie, that one, innit?
Oi, Phil. Are those sausages coming?
Almost ready.
We just need a bit more salt.
Huh?
Incredible. It's a new species.
What the bloody hell are those things? It's like a gnome shagged a mushroom.
They're absolutely adorable.
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable. And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things.
We'd be famous.
Get on MTV. I wonder what they taste like.
Oh, we really shouldn't disrupt their habitat.
Right. Sure, sure.
Greetings.
Welcome, friends. I'll be right down.
Could I interest you in some peppermint tea?
What are you guys?
We are sprites. We sprite balance to the forest. We take care of the animals.
Guys, guys.
Hey, little mushroom geezer. You call with us camping here for the night?
Absolutely. A friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites.
Maybe it was just ketchup or something, like red paint.
Maybe they were just painting their little hats or something.
Guys, guys, guys, this isn't funny.
Guys?
We were just going to catch one with their psycho. They're going to get me out of this hurry. They're going to kill us.
Hurry.
Left for leaf and story.
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches.
Spray them.
Spray this.
No, no, no.
Sweet cake.
Is that?
Yes, yes.
I don't want to hurt you. Just just keep your distance.
All right, then, eat salty little green bastards.
Those punks treated the world as their own personal rubbish bin, and you set them free. Now you join them.
No, no, no, no.
I'll give you that one, brother bird.
All right, sprites, let's burn the bodies and have some peppermint tea.
Danger, danger, I'm a forest ranger, about and clear the way. I'm about to blast it, stick like plastic, what's your mama gonna say?
I'm about to drop it, stanky, plop it, I'm just catching steam. Now pillage and loot it, I'm a polluted lake to the river, to the stream.
I'll borrow a little dearie and call me cavalierie, try to cut me down to size.
Loyalty's my announcer, driver, bouncer, bakin' me cakes and pies.
Yeah, this camp is a call out, here come the fallout, me and my crew don't play.
My boos on the log, on the leaf, on the frog, cut walls and the trees to say, hey, hey, hey.
Sick and sick and rough, sick and rough.