I can't believe we've got to stop with the truth, I can't believe we've got to stop with the truth.
If I have to hear the latter name for one more animal, I swear I'm going to kill it.
Relax, Sugarbun. While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun.
Yeah, and get wasted out of our minds. Where are you, man?
Come on, team. We mustn't tell you, Dally, when there's so much nature to see.
I was thinking, we should call our class project fun guys that are forest.
Get it? Because we're a group of fun guys, and also fun guys.
Shush, nothing no one to. And she's in distress.
There, then we need two motors in a flower.
So, look at your goo.
Wow. Out of the way, talk what? We're camping here.
Finally, time to get that barbecue burning.
Oh, oh dear.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
And easy guys, we're supposed to be studying nature, not wrecking it.
A piss break!
Bam, damn it.
Oh, bam, bam.
Boy, fungus free, make yourself useful and fix the ten.
They've been to friendly campsite ribbing.
Fun.
Ah, she went to five five minutes alone in these woods.
Oh, yeah. She's a real weeny that one in it.
Boy, Phil. Ah, no sausage is coming.
Almost ready.
We're going to need a bit more show.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Where are we wrong?
I wonder what kind of species.
Bloody hell with those things.
It's like a no-shaper mushroom.
Don't bring us up to the day of fun
Bring me up, yay, yay, yay
Bring me to the classroom where we run
Yay, we're absolutely adorable
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things
We'd be famous
Get on MTV
I wonder what they taste like
We really shouldn't disrupt their habitat
Right
Sure
Greatings
Welcome friends
I'll be right down
It's good I interest you in some peppermint tea
What are you guys?
We are sprayed
We spray balanced to the forest
We take care of the animals
Plants
Guys
Huh?
Hey, a little mushroom geezer
You call with us camping here for the night?
Absolutely
A friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites
Maybe it was just ketchup or something like red paint?
Yeah, maybe they were just painting their little hats or something
Guys
Guys, this isn't funny
Nice
We're just going to catch one
But they're psycho
You've got to get me out of these hurry
You must be ready to go
Hurry
Take them there for leaf and stone
You pick the wrong camping spot bitches
Spray time
Hurry
We progress
Place it
we've come
We have come
We need more
So on
Ministers
we'll come
We'll come
We mini
WeECH
We are
Oh!
She has a wife now, baby!
Oh, get it off!
Sweet face!
Oh, no!
No, no, no!
Oh!
What?
It's not!
No!
Oh!
It's not!
No!
Oh!
Oh, it's not!
I got a swim!
Oh, it's weird!
Oh, oh!
Oh, ah!
Rally,
I don't want to hurt you, just keep your distance!
Alright then, it's all too little green faucets!
Ah!
Those punks treated the world as a long personal rubbish bin!
And you won't set them free!
Now you're join them!
I'll give you that one, brother bird!
Alright, sprites!
Let's burn the bodies and have some peppermint tea!
Giving us where every road can I be, I believe, before it's still so happy!
Oh, oh, ha ha!
Be all together now!
Spread these friends with the sun!
Drink these friends with the sun!
Drink these friends with the moon!
We will suck to the day as well!
Drink the eye, eye, eye, eye, eye, eye!
Dang it, danger!
I'm a forest ranger, about and clear the way!
I'm about to blast it, stick right plastic!
What am I gonna say?
Whoa!
The drop is stanky, drop it!
I'ma just catch and scream!
Now pillage and move it!
I'm up all loaded!
Link to the river to the stream!
What's up?
Whoa, a little deerie!
They call me cavalry!
Try to cut me down two sides!
Look at this, my announcer driver!
About to pick me cakes and thighs!
Yeah, this camp is a cannot!
You come to follow me and my crew, don't they?
My peers on the log, I know they've found their files,
cut walls in the tree to set!
Hey, hey!
It's a hero!