Oh, you cute little corny little sparsome.
Blatanty.
Bonus points.
Ugh, can't believe we got stuck with a tree hugger.
If I have to hear the Latin name for one more animal, I swear I'm going to kill her.
Relax sugar puns, while she does all the work, we'll have all the fun.
Yeah, and get wasted out of our minds.
Way ahead of you, man.
Come on team, we mustn't dilly-dally when there's so much nature to see.
I was thinking, we should call our class project Fun Guys in a Forest.
Get it?
Because we're a group of fun guys, and also fun guys.
Shush!
That's a low-wage tale, and she's in distress.
There they are, my little Montesilaf larva.
Oh, look at her go.
Wow.
Out of the way, dork-wad.
We're camping here.
Finally.
Time to get that barbecue burning.
Oh, oh dear.
Gross.
Easy guys, we're supposed to be studying nature, not wrecking it.
Piss break.
Oi, fungus freak, make yourself useful and fix the tent.
Oh, a bit of friendly campsite ribbing.
Fun.
She wouldn't survive five minutes alone in these woods.
Yeah, she's a real weenie that one, innit?
Oi, Phil, our new sausage is coming.
Almost ready.
We just need a bit more salt.
Incredible, it's a new species.
What the bloody hell are those things?
It's like a note shagged a mushroom.
They're absolutely adorable.
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable.
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things.
We'd be famous.
Get on MTV.
I wonder what they taste like.
Oh, we really shouldn't disrupt their habitat.
Right.
Should we?
We should.
Right, sure, sure.
Greetings.
Welcome, friends.
I'll be right down.
Could I interest you in some peppermint tea?
What are you guys?
We're sprites.
We sprite balance to the forest.
Take care of the animals.
Squants, birds, swans, ladybugs.
Squirrels, bees, squirrels, a small, small species of grass.
Hey, little mushroom geezer, you call with us
camping here for the night?
Absolutely.
A friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites.
Maybe it was just ketchup or something like red paint.
Yeah, maybe they were just painting
their little hats or something.
Guys?
Guys, this isn't funny.
We were just going to catch one, but they're psycho.
They've got to get me out of these hurry.
They've got to kill us.
Hurry.
Wait for the F for leaf and stone.
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches.
Spray them!
Run!
You little freaks!
Spray this!
Yeah!
Oh my God!
Sugarman! Sugarman, help me!
Sweet cake!
No!
No, no, please!
What?
Is that...
No!
No, no, no!
I can't swim, I can't swim!
Yes, yes!
No! No!
Suckers, I sprained you!
I don't want to hurt you, just keep your distance!
Alright then, eat salt you little green bastards!
Those punks treated the world as their own personal rubbish bin, and you set them free! Now you'll join them!
Suckers!
I'll give you that one, Brother Bird!
Alright Sprites, let's burn the bunnies and have some peppermint tea!
Danger, danger! I'm a forest ranger, about and clear the way!
I'm about to blast it, stick like plastic, what your mama gonna say?
I'm about to drop it, stanky, plop it, I'mma just catch you in steam!
Now pillage, and nude it, I'mma pollute it, lake to the river, to the stream, push, pop!
Pull you a little dearie, then call me Cavalieri, try to cut me down to size!
Now there's my announcer, driver, bouncer, baking me cakes and pies!
Yeah this camp is a call out, here come the fall out, me and my crew don't play!
My poos on the log, on the leaf, on the frog, cut words and the truth to say! Hey! Hey! Hey!
City kid, city kid, run! City kid, run! City kid, city kid, run! City kid run!