CONGRAMERAL STARES
Easy and thin
Hello Mr..Snail
You cute little corny-w象
And Candy
B let me
Oh, I can't believe we got to stop with a tree, Hugga.
If I have to hear the Latin name for one more animal,
I swear I'm going to kill her.
Relax to the bun.
While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun.
Yeah, I get wasted out of our minds.
Where are you, man?
Come on, team.
We mustn't dilly, Dally, when there's so much nature to see.
I'm thinking we should call our class project,
fun guys that are boys.
Get it? Because we're a group of fun guys, and also fun guys.
Shush!
That's the Latin, and she's in distress.
There's a little more to set up lava.
So, let me show you.
Wow.
Out of the way, talk what?
We're camping here.
Finally.
Turn to get that barbecue burning.
Oh.
Oh, dear.
Ah.
Oh, God.
Easy guys, what's the purpose of studying nature?
Not breaking it.
Pist-break.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
Oh.
Oi, fungers freak.
Make yourself useful, and fix the tent.
Oh.
They've been a friendly camp site ribbing.
Oh, my God.
She went to my five minutes alone in these woods.
Oh, yeah.
She's a real weeny that won't in it.
Oi, Phil.
Oh, no sausages coming.
Almost ready.
We're going to eat a bit more so.
It's like a no-shagged mushroom.
Yeah, absolutely adorable.
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable.
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things.
We be famous.
Get on MTV.
I wonder what they taste like.
Oh, we really shouldn't disrupt that habitat.
Right.
Sure.
Great thing.
What?
Welcome friends.
I'll be right down.
Good eye interest you in some peppermint tea.
What?
What are you guys?
We are sprites.
We sprate balance to the forest.
We take care of the animals.
We're sprites.
What?
Well, guys, guys.
Hey, a little mushroom gaser.
You call with us camping in for the night?
Absolutely.
A friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites.
Maybe it was just catch up or something like red paint?
Yeah, maybe they were just...
painting their little hats or something.
Guys?
Guys, this isn't funny.
Nice.
We're just going to catch one.
But they're psycho.
We've got to get me out of these hurry.
We can't get up anymore.
We have to walk about now.
We've got to go now.
For the folk with historic wind...
You pick the wrong camping spot, bitches.
S sólo!
You want a run?
S müsst!
Spone!
No!
I'm gonna go to the morning soon!
Oh!
Oh, no!
No!
She got the words for her!
We can't!
No!
Oh!
Oh, it's you.
It's me.
I can't breathe.
What?
Is that it?
No.
No, no, no.
I can't breathe.
Oh, yes, yes.
No.
I'm going to scratch.
I don't want to hurt you.
Just keep not distance.
All right, then.
It's all too little green fosters.
Ha!
Those punks treat at the one that's her own personal rubbish bin.
And you don't shut them free.
Now you're joining them.
Ha!
I'll give you that one, brother bird.
All right, Sprite, let's burn the bodies and have some peppermint tea.
The drop is stinky, drop it, I'm a just catch and sting.
Now pillage and lint it, I'm a ballad, it lake to the river to best dream.
I'll give you that one, brother bird.
If you are sitting here, I'll take it around the world.