Hello, Mr. Snail! Oh, you cute little corny wasp-ersome!
Lightning! Bonus points!
Can't believe we got stuck with the tree-hugger. If I have to hear the Latin name for one more animal, I swear I'm going to kill her!
Relax, Sugar Buns! While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun!
Yeah, and get wasted out of our minds! Way ahead of you, man!
Come on, team! We mustn't dilly-dally when there's so much nature to see!
I was thinking, we should call our class project, Funguys in a Forest!
Get it? Because we're a group of fun-guys and also fun-guys!
Shush! That's a low-word, team! And she's in distress!
There, there, my little Monticello flower!
Oh, look at her go! Wow!
Out of the way, talkwad! We're camping here!
Finally! Time to get that barbecue burning!
Oh, oh dear!
Gross!
Easy, guys! We're supposed to be studying nature, not wrecking it!
Piss break!
Oi! Fungus-free! Make yourself useful and fix the tent!
Oh, a bit of friendly campsite ribbing! Fun!
She wouldn't survive five minutes alone in these woods!
Yeah, she's a real weenie, that one, innit?
Oi, Phil! Arno sausages coming!
Almost ready! Just need a bit more salt.
It's incredible! It's a new species!
What the bloody hell are those things?
It's like a gnome shagged a mushroom!
They're absolutely adorable!
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable!
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things!
We'd be famous!
Get on MTV! I wonder what they taste like!
Oh, we really shouldn't disrupt their habitat!
Right! Sure, sure!
Greetings! Welcome, friends! I'll be right down!
Could I interest you in some peppermint tea?
What are you guys?
We are sprites! We sprite balance to the forest!
We take care of the animals, plants, birds...
Guys! Guys!
Hey, little mushroom-geezer!
You call with us camping here for the night?
Absolutely! A friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites!
Maybe it was just ketchup or something like red paint?
Yeah, maybe they were just painting their little hats or something.
Guys?
Guys, this isn't funny!
We were just going to catch one, but they're psycho!
You've got to get me out of this! Hurry! They're gonna kill us!
Hurry!
Right foot, left foot, leaf and stone!
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches!
Sprite them!
Oh
I
Don't want to hurt you just just keep your distance. All right, then
Oh
Those punks treated the world as their own personal rubbish bin and you set them free now
Give you that one brother bird. All right sprites. Let's burn the bodies and have some
Peppermint tea
Danger danger, I'm a forest ranger about and clear the way
I'm about to blast it stick like plastic. What's your mama gonna say?
Drop it stanky flop it. I'm just catching steam now pillage and
Lake to the river to the stream
A little dearie and call me Cavalier. Try to cut me down to size
There's my announcer driver bouncer baking me cakes and pies
I
You