Hello, Mr. Snail!
Oh, you cute little corny wasperson, that name!
Bonespoint!
Ugh!
Can't believe we got stuck with the tree!
I'll start with a tree hugger.
If I have to hear the Latin name for one more animal,
I swear I'm gonna kill her.
Relax, sugar buns.
While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun.
Yeah, I get wasted out of our minds.
Where are you, man?
Come on, team, we mustn't dilly dally
when there's so much nature to see.
I was thinking we should call our class project
fun guys in a forest.
Get it?
Because we're a group of fun guys and also fun guys.
Josh, nothing no right to you, and she's in distress.
There are little monsters in a flower.
Oh, look at her go.
Wow.
Out of the way, talk, what?
We're camping here.
Finally.
Time to get that barbecue burning.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
The ash.
Oh.
Oh, oh, ah.
Hello.
Easy guys, we're supposed to be studying nature not
wrecking it.
Keys brake.
shaped.
Ben, Ben, Ben, Ben, Ben.
Oh.
Oi.
Fungus free.
Make yourself useful and fix the tent.
Oh.
I put a friendly campsite ribbing.
Fun.
US.
She went to five, five minutes alone in these woods.
Oh, yeah.
She's a real weeny that one in it.
Oi, Phil, I don't know sausage is coming.
Almost ready.
We're going to need a bit more salt.
Ugh.
Huh?
It's so.
It's incredible, it's a new species.
What?
A bloody hell of those things.
Be Frankie young, and we will stop to the day of fun
Frankie, I am young, I am young
We do watch the day we run
Frankie, we do
Yeah! They're absolutely adorable!
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable!
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things.
We'd be famous!
Get on MTV! I wonder what they taste like?
No, we really shouldn't disrupt their habitat.
Why? Sure, sure.
Greetings!
Welcome, friends! I'll be right down!
Could I interest you in some peppermint tea?
What are you guys?
We are sprites! We sprite balanced to the forest!
We take care of the animals!
Scratch!
What?
Oh, geez!
Oh, guys! Guys!
Huh?
Oh, this is a grass!
Hey, uh, little mushroom geezer!
You call with us camping here for the night?
Absolutely!
A friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites!
Maybe, maybe it was just sketch up or something like red paint?
Yeah, maybe they were just painting their little hats
or something.
Guys?
Guys!
Guys, this isn't funny!
Guys?
Yum yum yum!
You can catch me when we die!
Three, three, go!
Wait, we're just gonna catch one!
With their psycho!
You've gotta get me out of these hurrys!
Say, can we kill us?
Three, three, go!
Wait!
We've been stalling!
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches!
Spray time!
Oh!
It's like the rocks!
The rocks!
AHHHH!
AHH!
Hey!
AHHHH!
AHH!
Go!
Oh!
Not that hard, stop!
No!
Get it out!
Sweet taste!
Don't chop it!
When?
Oh FTS!
You know.
What is that?
No!
I'm all scared.
Yes!
No!
Oh...
Aah!
There's a sprite here!
There's a sprite!
Aah!
I don't want to hurt you!
Just keep your distance!
Aah!
All right then!
Eat salty little green faucets!
Aah!
Look!
Those punks treated the world as her own personal rubbish bin, and you set them free.
Now you'll join them.
I'll give you that one, brother bird.
All right, sprites, let's burn the bodies and have some peppermint tea.
I'll give you that one.
Danger danger, I'm a forest ranger, about and clear the way.
I'm about to blast this stick right plastic, what you're gonna say.
I'm about to drop it, stanky, drop it, I'mma just catch and scream.
Now pillage, and nude it, I'm a polluted lake to the river to the stream for spa.
I'm a little deary, and call me cavalry, try to cut me down to size.
Low of these, my announcer, driver, bouncer, bacon, make cakes and thighs.
This camp is a colored, here come the fall out, me and my crew don't play.
My boots on the log and the leaf on the frog cut, was in the tree, do you say hey hey?
Take it to your own, take it to your own, take it to your own, take it to your own.
You