Hello, Mr. Snail! Oh, you cute little corny wasp-ersome!
Lightning! Bonus points!
Can't believe we got stuck with the tree-hugger. If I have to hear the Latin name for one more animal, I swear I'm going to kill her!
Relax, Sugar Buns! While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun!
Yeah, and get wasted out of our minds! Way ahead of you, man!
Come on, team! We mustn't dilly-dally when there's so much nature to see!
I was thinking, we should call our class project, Funguys in a Forest!
Get it? Because we're a group of fun-guys and also fun-guys!
Shush! That's a low-word, team! And she's in distress!
There, there, my little Monticello flower!
Oh, look at her go! Wow!
Out of the way, talkwad! We're camping here!
Finally! Time to get that barbecue burning!
Oh, oh dear!
Gross!
Easy, guys! We're supposed to be studying nature, not wrecking it!
Piss break!
Oi! Fungus-free! Make yourself useful and fix the tent!
Oh, a bit of friendly campsite ribbing! Fun!
She wouldn't survive five minutes alone in these woods!
Yeah, she's a real weenie, that one, innit?
Oi, Phil! Arno sausages coming!
Almost ready! Just need a bit more salt.
It's incredible! It's a new species!
What the bloody hell are those things?
It's like a gnome shagged a mushroom!
They're absolutely adorable!
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable!
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things!
We'd be famous!
Get on MTV! I wonder what they taste like!
Oh, we really shouldn't disrupt their habitat!
Right! Sure, sure!
Greetings! Welcome, friends! I'll be right down!
Could I interest you in some peppermint tea?
What are you guys?
We are sprites! We sprite balance to the forest!
We take care of the animals, plants, birds...
Guys! Guys!
Hey, little mushroom-geezer!
You call with us camping here for the night?
Absolutely! A friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites!
Maybe it was just ketchup or something like red paint?
Yeah, maybe they were just painting their little hats or something.
Guys?
Guys, this isn't funny!
We were just going to catch one, but they're psycho!
We've got to get me out of these! Hurry! They're gonna kill us!
Hurry!
Right for left for leaf and stone!
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches!
Sprite them!
Take that, you little freaks!
Sprite this!
Help!
Help! Fire!
Oh my God!
Don't look! Don't look! Don't look!
Sugar boy! Sugar boy, help me!
Help me!
Sugar!
Weakling!
No!
No, stop it!
What?
Is that?
No!
I can't swim!
Yes! Yes!
No!
I don't want to hurt you!
Just keep your distance!
Alright then!
You little green bastard!
Those punks treated the world as their own personal rubbish bin!
And you set them free!
Now you'll join them!
I'll give you that one, brother bird!
Alright Sprites, let's burn the bodies and have some peppermint tea!
And keep in touch wherever we roam! Daddy bee, daddy billy, the forest is our happy home!
Sprite this, Sprite Sprite, lick the sun! Sprite the bees, Sprite the gum!
And we won't stop till the day is done! Sprite the eye-eye-eye-yum-yum!
Danger! Danger! I'm a forest ranger! About and clear the way!
I'm about to blast this stick like plastic! What's your mama gonna say?
I'm about to drop it, stanky, plop it! I'mma just catch you in steam!
Now pillaged and looted, I'mma pollute it! Lake to the river, to the stream, full spunk!
We were little deary, then called me cavaliery, tried to cut me down to size!
Now there's my announcer, driver, bouncer, bakin' me cakes and pies!
Yeah, this camp is a call-out, here come the fallout, me and my crew don't play!
My proof's on the log, on the leaf, on the frog, cut words and the truth to say!
Syndicate, syndicate, roll! Syndicate, roll!