Hello Mr. Snail! Oh, you cute little corny was sparsome. That name, bonus points!
Oh, can't believe we got stuck with a tree hugger. If I have to hear the latter name for one more animal, I swear I'm gonna kill her.
Relax sugar buns. While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun.
Yeah, and get wasted out of our minds. Where are you man?
Come on team, we mustn't dilly-dally when there's so much nature to see. I was thinking we should call our class project fun guys in a forest.
Get it? Because we're a group of fun guys, and also fun guys. Shush!
That's the yellow bird team, and she's in distress!
There they are, my little Monticello flower.
Oh, look at her go. Wow.
Out of the way, Dorkwood. We're camping here.
Finally. Time to get that barbecue burning.
Oh, oh, oh dear.
Easy guys, we're supposed to be studying nature, not wrecking it.
Piss break!
Oi, fungus freak, make yourself useful and fix the tent.
Oh, a bit of friendly campsite ribbing. Fun.
She wouldn't survive five minutes alone in these woods.
Yeah, she's a real weenie that one, innit?
Oi, Phil, no sausages coming.
Almost ready. Just need a bit more salt.
It's incredible. It's a new species.
What the bloody hell are those things? It's like a note shagged a mushroom.
Oh, they're absolutely adorable.
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable.
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things.
We'll be famous.
Get on MTV. I wonder what they taste like.
Oh, we really shouldn't disrupt their habitat.
Right. Sure.
Sure.
Greetings. Welcome, friends. I'll be right down.
Could I interest you in some peppermint tea?
What are you guys?
We are sprites. We sprites balanced to the forest.
We take care of the animals.
Squants.
Birds.
Guys. Guys.
Hey, uh, little mushroom geezer. You call with us camping here for the night?
Absolutely. A friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites.
Maybe, maybe it was just ketchup or something like red.
Yeah, maybe they were just painting their little hats or something.
Guys.
Guys, this isn't funny.
I am lost.
We've been watching the wind.
Friendly, free, friendly, go.
We're going to the forest.
Let's go.
Guys, we're just going to catch one, right there's a psycho.
They'll be out of this hurry. They're going to kill us.
Free, friendly, go.
Really?
Right foot left for leave and store.
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches.
Spray time.
No!
Time for a little flicks.
Let's try this!
Fire!
Oh my god!
Shagamon! Shagamon! Help me!
Wait, Shagamon!
Shagamon!
What? Is that...
No! No!
I can't swim! I can't swim!
Yes! Yes!
No! No!
Shagamon! Shagamon!
I don't want to hurt you! Just keep your distance!
Alright then! Eat salty little green bastards!
Those punks treated the world as their own personal rubbish bin! And you set them free! Now you'll join them!
Oh my god!
I'll give you that one, brother bird!
Alright sprites! Let's burn the bunnies and have some peppermint tea!
Give me much where every room,
Gah-ee-ee, Gah-ee, Billy, the forest is our happy home!
Ho-ho-ha-ha, we all together now!
Sprites, sprites, sprites, like the sun!
Spraint-ee-ee, spraint-ee-um,
We will stop till the day is fun!
Spraint-ee-ee, ay-ay-ay-ay-yum-yum!
Danger, danger! I'm a forest ranger!
About and clear the way!
I'm about to blast it, stick like plastic!
What's your mama gonna say?
I'm about to drop it, stanky plop it!
I'ma just catch you in steam!
Now pillage and loot it!
I'ma pollute it!
Lake to the river to the stream!
We'll spot!
We're a little deary and call me Cavaliery!
Try to cut me down to size!
One of these my announcer, driver, bouncer!
Bacon made cakes and pies!
Yeah, this camp is a cut-out!
Here come the fallout!
Me and my crew don't play!
My booze on the log and the leaf on the fire!
Cut words in the tree to say!
Hey, hey, hey!
Sing it, sing it, rock!
Sing it, rock!