Hello, Mr. Snail!
Oh, you cute little corny-ass person!
That name, bonus points!
Oh, can't believe we got stuck with a trick!
Oh, no, Mr. Snail!
Oh, you cute little corny-ass person!
That name, bonus points!
Oh, can't believe we got stuck with a trick!
Oh, can't believe we got stuck with a tree hugger!
If I have to hear the latter name for one more animal, I swear I'm going to kill him!
Relax, sugar buns!
While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun!
Yeah, and get wasted out of our minds!
Where are you, man?
Come on, team! We mustn't dilly dally when there's so much nature to see!
I was thinking, we should call our class project, fun guys and a forest!
Get it?
Because we're a group of fun guys and also fun guys!
Shush!
That's the no-what team!
And she's into stress!
There's a little mountain of lava!
Oh, look at your goo!
Wow!
Out of the way, talk what?
We're camping here!
Finally!
It's time to get that barbecue, Bernie!
Oh, oh, oh, dude!
Ah!
Oh!
And easy guys, was supposed to be studying nature and not wrecking it!
Piss!
Oh, damn it!
Oi! Fungus Freak!
Make yourself useful and fix the tent!
A bit of friendly campsite ribbing!
She went to five, five minutes alone in these woods.
Oh yeah, she's a real weenie that one in it.
Oi, Phil.
Ah, no sausages coming.
Almost ready.
She did a bit more so.
What a bloody hell with those things.
It's like a no-shack to mushroom.
Yeah, absolutely adorable.
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable.
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things.
We'll be famous.
Get on MTV.
I wonder what they taste like.
Let's rock the habitat.
Right.
Sure, sure.
Greetings.
Welcome, friends.
I'll be right down.
Could I interest you in some pepperminty?
What are you guys?
We are Sprites.
We Sprite balanced to the forest.
We take care of the animals.
What?
Guys, guys.
Hey, a little mushroom gaza.
You call with us camping here for the night?
Absolutely.
A friend of the forest is a friend of the Sprites.
Maybe it was just ketchup or something like red paint?
Yeah, maybe they were just painting their little hats or something.
Guys.
Guys, this isn't funny.
We're just going to catch one.
But they're psycho.
You've got to get me out of these hurry.
Sprite me go.
Hurry up.
Wait for me.
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches.
Sprite time.
Sprite.
Fresh air.
Oh, no!
Oh!
No!
She had to wipe her open!
Oh!
No!
We're safe!
Oh!
Huh?
No!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey!
I'm going to destroy this community!
No!
It's insane!
NO!
No!
It's not!
No, no!
I can't!
No!
I can't.
Help!
Hello!
Open the door!
He's no distance!
All right then, it's all too little green fastest!
Oh!
Those punks treated the world as their own personal rubbish bin!
And you won't set them free!
Now you'll join them!
I'll give you that one, brother bird!
All right, Sprite, let's burn the bodies and have some peppermint tea!
Giving us where every wrong daddy, daddy Billy, before his tears are happy home!
Sprite, Sprite, Sprite's with the sun!
Sprite, Sprite, let's burn the bodies and have some peppermint tea!
Danger, danger, I'm a forest ranger about and clear the way!
I'm about to blast this stick like plastic, what am I gonna say?
I'm about to drop it, stanky, drop it!
I'm about to just catch you in steam!
Now pillage and need it, I'm about to loot it!
Lake to the river to the stream, we'll spawn!
I'm a little dearie, and call me Cavalry!
Try to cut me down to size!
Look at these, my announcer, driver!
Bouncer, bakein' me cakes and pies!
Yeah, this camp is a collapse, you come to fall out!
Me and my crew don't dare!
My crew's on the log, and they'll link from the file cut!
Wars and the truth, you sick!
Hey, hey, hey!
Get it, get it, get it wrong!
Get it, get it wrong!
Take it, run, run!